harvardgenerator.com 2018-12-19

# Harvard Referencing Generator | Privacy Policy

Looking after your personal data is very important and we want you to be confident that your data is safe and secure with us.

This Privacy Policy has been written to help you better understand how your Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is being used on our website. 

### What personal information do we collect from you?

We only request necessary information from you and we will try to ensure that your details are accurate and kept up to date.

When registering, donating or using our contact form you will be asked to enter your full name and email address to help personalise your experience.

### When do we collect personal information?

We collect personal information from you when you register on our site, donate or fill out the contact form.

### How do we use your personal information?

We may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * To personalise your experience on our website.
  * To respond to customer service requests.
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

### How do we protect your information?

Your personal information is stored behind a secured network and is only accessible by a limited number of people who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

Transactions are processed using a secure gateway provider and payment details are not stored or processed on our servers.

Passwords are encrypted and will never be sent via email. You must keep your password safe and you must not disclose it to anyone. You can change your password by [logging into your account](http://www.harvardgenerator.com/account/login).

You must tell us immediately if you believe a third-party has obtained your password. You can also [reset your password](http://www.harvardgenerator.com/account/forgotten-password).

### Do we sell or share your personal information?

No. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Should you wish to remove any information that we may have recorded about you, please [contact us](http://www.harvardgenerator.com/contact).

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. We use cookies to help us remember your references and allow you to login to our website. Cookies are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We also use cookies to:

  * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
  * Keep track of advertisements.
  * Save your references.
  * Allow you to login.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. If you turn cookies off it will disable some features of the site.

### Advertising

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website. Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you can contact us using our [contact form](http://www.harvardgenerator.com/contact).

_Last updated: May 21st 2018._
